Alexis Y Sanabria

Full Stack Developer

Full Stack Web Developer able to build a sophisticated web application with a full database backend all the way from mockup to rollout. Adept at working with diverse teams to implement projects. Also experienced in all project phases using Agile Methodologies. Extremely punctual, responsible, reliable, hard worker, quick learner and very well organized.

EXPERIENCE

Elite Digital - (Lead Full stack Developer) Toronto,, ON Dec 2021 - June 2024

 Successfully led and contributed to multiple projects, overseeing their creation and ongoing maintenance.
 Developed project plans, allocated resources, and ensured timely completion. Collaborated with cross-functional teams to enhance project functionality and user experience. Implemented effective problem-solving strategies to address project challenges and issues.

Isara (Through Aerotek/AcTalent) - (Full stack Developer Remote) Waterloo, ON Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

- Collaborated to the Advance Project by coding, debugging, and testing the back-end and front-end, within a team of 30 other developers/testers.
- Provided code reviews to other team members branches before merging them with the base code.

Amazing Pet Grooming - (Graphic Designer / Web Developer) Milton, ON 2016 - 2020

- Designed and developed compelling logos, flyers, and additional marketing materials.
- Designed a Full-stack-app to improve the way of handling clients and employees schedule
- Solved customer issues / IT related issues on a daily basis.

PRIVATE PROJECT COLLABORATION

Isara Advance Crypto Agility Suite *Cryptographic* management platform:

https://www.isara.com/products/isara-advance-crypto-agility-suite.html
Enterprise solution for managing, discovering, and remediating cryptographic infrastructures within organizations.

905-299-2366

alexisvep@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://www.alexisysanabria.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexis-sanabria-8000

2574/

Github: https://github.com/alexisyepes Cambridge, ON N1T-1]8

BUILT PROJECTS

Web Application *Full Management System* https://www.amazingpetgrooming.ca/

This React/Node Application was built for a Pet Grooming business. The admin of the page is able to add employees into the system, so they can login to the private pages based on their roles, where they can manage the clients' database, add appointments to their own Calendars and adjust their working hours. Customers are also able to book appointments online. This Application solved several issues this business faced in the past.

SKILLS

FRONT-END BACK-END React **NodeIs Typescript Express** Next Is MvSOL PostgreSQL **Javascript** HTML MongoDB CSS/SASS FaunaDB **CSS Modules** Sanity Bootstrap GraphQL **JQuery** Solr Handlebars NodeMailer

Handlebars NodeMailer Rest API Postmark Apollo Client Sendgrid

Firebase Jwt Authentication

Shopify / Liquid Passport Js

Cypress Testing

MOBILE AWS

DEVELOPMENT Google Cloud

React Native

OTHER TECHNOLOGIES / SKILLS

Git Version Control

Git Bash

MVC Pattern

Data/Sites Migration

Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects

Bilingual: Spanish/English

EDUCATION

University of Toronto, Toronto, ON Full-stack Web Development Bootcamp 2018-2019 An intensive bootcamp, dedicated to designing and building full stack web applications.

Compu-Ingenieros, Bogota, COL Computer Programming Program 2002-2003

Two year program dedicated to computer programming fundamentals using Visual Basic, as well as computer maintenance, and graphic design: Photoshop/Illustrator.